# morgan evans

#### ux prototyper

Professional background and passion for the sweet spot between front end development and user experience design. I strive to rapidly bring designs to life to help make products more simplified, user-friendly and aesthetically pleasing in this world of information overload.

## work experience

#### Adobe

**Experience Developer** 

Jan 2019 - Present

Collaborate with the UX designers to offer technical feedback prior to implementation, then work alongside another front end developer to implement new features in our web application. Languages include Elm, JS, ReactJS, CSS and HTML.

**Experience Designer Developer** 

Oct 2016 - Jan 2019

UX designer and front end developer for an Adobe v1.0 web application. Technical skills include Elm, HTML, CSS, interaction and visual design, user research and rapid prototyping. Also, hired, trained and mentored the team's 2018/2019 interns.

#### **Nordstrom**

**UX** Design Intern

June - Aug 2016

Collaborate with UX designers to help redesign the Nordstrom internal POS system, as well as the N.com left navigation bar. This required rapid prototyping and peer reviews with developers to assist with design integration.

#### **Learn Together**

UX Designer & Front End Developer

Nov 2015 - April 2016

Lead the UX process to provide the Learn Together web application with a usable and consistent UI. Including building workflow diagrams and wireframes, rapid prototyping, and web development involving HTML, CSS, AngularJS and Bootstrap.

## education

#### **University of Washington**

B.S. Informatics (HCI) / Minor in French

2011 - 2016

Solid understanding of development, design principles and information management. Proficient with front end development and cross-platform user experience design.

**Extracurriculars:** Informatics Admissions Board, Informatics Programming Committee, Women in Informatics, Pi Beta Phi Sorority

Achievements: Dean's List for Autumn 2012/13/15, Winter 2013/16, Spring 2013/16

### contact

Seattle, WA 425.577.9678 evansmorg@gmail.com

## links

evansmorgan.com linkedin.com/in/evansmn github.com/mnevans

## programming

HTML/CSS JavaScript Elm React, jQuery PHP Bootstrap

## design

Web Design Mobile Design Interaction Design Rapid Prototyping Animation User Research

#### software

Adobe Creative Suite Microsoft Office Suite Atom Sketch Github InVision